Guide to the David Wolf Collection of American Musical Theater
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
David Wolf Collection of American Musical Theater
1953-2000
YCAL MSS 867
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
23.75
(29 boxes)
Wolf, David
Arrangement
Arranged by type of material.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 11-22 (audiocassettes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Lonny Price, 2005.
David Wolf (1947-2005)
David Wolf was a member of the New York performing arts community. He worked for the stage director Harold Prince as a stage manager and assistant casting director for musical theater productions including Company, Follies, and A Little Night Music in the early 1970s; as a writer for the children's television series, The Unicorn Tales, for which he won an Emmy Award in 1978; and in other capacities in the entertainment industry. From childhood he was a collector of musical theater recordings and memorabilia, an interest that continued throughout his life.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of stage and film scripts and musical theater librettos, including early versions of Stephen Sondheim's unproduced Saturday Night (circa 1954) through Assassins (1990), as well as early versions of Harold Prince shows beginning with Cabaret (1966); audio recordings of musical theater and film productions, performances by individual singers, and interviews and presentations by directors, composers and performers; and scrapbooks containing newspaper clippings, photographs, production programs, and other material relating to theater and film productions including Fiddler on the Roof, Cabaret, and A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum.
Musical theater -- United States; Musical theater producers and directors -- United States; Musicals -- Librettos; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Audiocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Librettos (documents for music) -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Musical theater producers and directors -- United States; Masteroff, Joe ( Cabaret); Prince, Harold, 1928-; Sondheim, Stephen ( Funny thing happened on the way to the forum); Sondheim, Stephen ( Assassins); Stein, Joseph ( Fiddler on the roof); Wolf, David
- Librettos and scripts
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  Scope and Contents
  Includes annotated and unannotated mimeographed and photocopied typescript librettos and scripts from musical theater, stage, and film productions.
  - "70, Girls, 70", undated (Box 1)
  - "Abracadabra", undated (Box 1)
  - "After the Fox", 1965 May (Box 1)
  - "Ain't Broadway Grand", 1991 December 1 (Box 1)
  - "Assassins", 1990 December 18 (Box 1)
  - "Baker Street", 1963 April (Box 1)
  - "The Baker's Wife", 1964 November (Box 1)
  - "Big Deal", 1985 December (Box 1)
  - "Bodo", undated (Box 1)
  - "The Boys from Syracuse", undated (Box 1)
  - "Breakfast at Tiffany's", undated (Box 1)
  - "By the Beautiful Sea", undated (Box 1)
  - "Cabaret", 1966 May 19 (Box 1)
  - "Cabaret", 1988 August 18 (Box 1)
  - "Cabaret," first draft screenplay, undated (Box 1)
  - "Candide", 1974 January (Box 1)
  - "Cat and Mouse", 1963 (Box 1)
  - "Celebration", 1968 (Box 2)
  - "Chicago," rehearsal, 1974 October 21 (Box 2)
  - "Clown Alley", 1970 (Box 2)
  - "Coco", 1969 December 18 (Box 2)
  - "Colette", undated (Box 2)
  - "Come Summer", 1968 December (Box 2)
  - "Company", 1970 April 26 (Box 2)
  - "Company," first draft, 1969 May (Box 2)
  - "Company," second draft, undated (Box 2)
  - "Company," third draft, 1969 November (Box 2)
  - "The Curse of Kulyenchikov", 1980 July (Box 2)
  - "Damn Yankees", 1993 January (Box 2)
  - "Daphne in Cottage D", undated (Box 2)
  - "The Day Before Spring", undated (Box 2)
  - "Divorce Me, Darling!", undated (Box 2)
  - "Do Re Mi", undated (Box 2)
  - "Donny Brook", 1961 (Box 2)
  - "Doonesbury," rehearsal, undated (Box 2)
  - "Dr. Voltaire's Candide," outline first, undated (Box 3)
  - "Dr. Voltaire's Candide," second draft, 1973 August 14 (Box 3)
  - "Drat! The Cat!", 1961 (Box 3)
  - "Duddy", 1983 December 24 (Box 3)
  - "Duddy", 1984 January 17 (Box 3)
  - "Duddy," final Ottawa version, 1984 May 31 (Box 3)
  - "Durante", undated (Box 3)
  - "Durante," first Canadian version, undated (Box 3)
  - "The Emperor of San Francisco", undated (Box 3)
  - "The Exception and the Rule", 1968 September 16 (Box 3)
  - "A Family Affair", 1959, undated; 2 (Box 3)
  - "The Fiddler on the Roof", 1964 September 22; 3 (Box 3)
  - "Flahooey", 1996 March 5 (Box 3)
  - "Flora, the Red Menace", 1965 July 12 (Box 3)
  - "Flora, the Red Menace", undated (Box 4)
  - "Follies", 1970-1971; 5 (Box 4)
  - "Foxy", undated (Box 4)
  - "Full Circle", undated (Box 4)
  - "A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum", 1965, undated; 3 (Box 4)
  - "Jules Feiffer", undated (Box 4)
  - "The Girl Who Came to Supper", undated (Box 4)
  - "The Girls Upstairs", undated (Box 4)
  - "The Girls Upstairs / Ostrow", 1968 April (Box 4)
  - "Golden Rainbow", undated (Box 4)
  - "Good Boy / Here's Where I Belong", undated (Box 4)
  - "The Good Soup", 1960 January 4 (Box 4)
  - "The Goodbye Girl," early draft, undated (Box 5)
  - "The Graduate", undated (Box 5)
  - "The Greeks Had a Cure for It", undated (Box 5)
  - "Greenwillow", undated (Box 5)
  - "Grind", 1984 September 28 (Box 5)
  - "Hallelujah Baby", 1977 (Box 5)
  - "Happiest Girl", undated (Box 5)
  - "The Happiest Girl in the World", undated; 2 (Box 5)
  - "Happy New Year!", 1979 May 3 (Box 5)
  - "A Hard Day's Night", undated (Box 5)
  - "Harry the Fourth, Parts 1-37", undated (Box 5)
  - "Heads Up", undated (Box 5)
  - "Hellzapoppin!", 1976 October 18 (Box 5)
  - "High Button Shoes", 1960 December 21 (Box 5)
  - "High Spirits", undated (Box 5)
  - "His Monkey Wife", undated (Box 5)
  - "House of Flowers", undated
  - "How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying", 1966, undated; 2 (Box 6)
  - "I Do! I Do!", 1966 (Box 6)
  - "I Remember Mama", undated (Box 6)
  - "Into the Woods", 1986 September 4 (Box 6)
  - "Irene", 1973 March 13 (Box 6)
  - "It's a Mad, Mad World", undated (Box 6)
  - "It's a Bird...It's a Plane...It's Superman", 1966 March 29 (Box 6)
  - "Juno", undated (Box 6)
  - "Kean", 1961 November 2 (Box 6)
  - "Kings and Cabbages / Zenda", undated (Box 6)
  - "Kiss Me, Stupid", undated (Box 6)
  - "La Cage Aux Folles", 1983 December 1 (Box 6)
  - "Laughter on the 23rd Floor", 1993 (Box 6)
  - "Leda Had a Little Swan", undated (Box 6)
  - "Lil Abner", undated (Box 7)
  - "A Little Night Music", 1972 October; 3 (Box 7)
  - "Lolita My Love / Boston", undated (Box 7)
  - "Love is Just Around the Corner", undated (Box 7)
  - "Love Life", 1990 March 12 (Box 7)
  - "Merlin", 1982 June 8 (Box 7)
  - "Merrily We Roll Along", 1980-1981; 3 (Box 7)
  - "The Moonlight File", undated (Box 7)
  - "Mr. Wonderful", undated (Box 7)
  - "The Mystery of Edwin Drood", 1984 December 12 (Box 7)
  - "A New Leaf", 1969 April 28 (Box 7)
  - "The Odd Couple", undated (Box 7)
  - "On the Town", undated (Box 8)
  - "On Your Toes", 1983 (Box 8)
  - "One, Two, Three", undated (Box 8)
  - "One, Two, Three, Four, Five", 1987 February 25 (Box 8)
  - "The Other Musical", 1971 November 29 (Box 8)
  - "Pacific Overtures", undated (Box 8)
  - "The Pajama Game", 1953 December 1 (Box 8)
  - "Pretty Belle", 1970 November (Box 8)
  - "Promenade", undated (Box 8)
  - "Rags", 1983-1986; 4 (Box 8)
  - "Redhead", undated (Box 8)
  - "Sail Away", 1961, undated; 2 (Box 8)
  - "Saturday Night", undated (Box 8)
  - "Saturday, Sunday, Monday", undated; 2 (Box 8)
  - "The Selling of the President", 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - "Señor Discretion", 1985 November 12 (Box 9)
  - "A Shot in the Dark", 1963 October 14 (Box 9)
  - "Smiling, the Boy Fell Dead", undated (Box 9)
  - "Smiles", 1972, undated; 3 (Box 9)
  - "Some of My Best Friends", undated (Box 9)
  - "Something for Everyone", 1968 November 24 (Box 9)
  - "Status Quo Vadis", 1967 (Box 9)
  - "Steambath", 1969 May 5 (Box 9)
  - "Sugar", undated (Box 9)
  - "A Swim in the Sea", undated (Box 9)
  - "Tattered Tom", undated (Box 9)
  - "Teahouse / Lovely Ladies, Kind Gentlemen", 1969 February 20 (Box 9)
  - "They Might Be Giants", 1960 September (Box 10)
  - "A Thousand Clowns", 1963 September 1 (Box 10)
  - "Tovarich", 1961 September 27 (Box 10)
  - "Tropicana", undated; 2 (Box 10)
  - "Up in Central Park", undated (Box 10)
  - "The Virgin of Tapercingo", 1987 April (Box 10)
  - "West Side Story", 1960, undated; 2 (Box 10)
  - "What's New Pussy Cat?", 1965 June (Box 10)
  - "Woman of the Year", undated (Box 10)
  - "The World of Henry Orient", 1963 May (Box 10)
  - "Yentl", 1981 September (Box 10)
  - "Zorba", 1986 October 30 (Box 10)
- Audiocassettes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 11-22: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Includes commercial and non-commercial recordings.
  Arranged alphabetically within three categories: Musicals, Composer/Singer, and Interviews.
  - Musicals
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - America Kicks Up Its Heels (Bill Finn/Charles Rubin) First Workshop, Act I, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611604)
    - Annie, cut-outs, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611612)
      A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
      Apples
      We Got Annie
      Just Wait
      That's the Way it Goes
      Parents
      I've Never Been So Happy
      Tomorrow
    - Arthur: The Musical, cut and paste of two versions, 1996 April; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611620)
    - Baby, sung by Richard Maltby/David Shire, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611638)
    - Ballroom, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611646)
    - Bring Back Birdie, Act I and II, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611653)
    - A Broadway Musical, Act I and II, 1978 October 20; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611661)
      Here in the Program
      A Broadway Musical
      I Hurry Home to You
      The 1934 Hot Chocolate Jazz Babies Revue
      Lawyers
      You Only Get One Chance
      Gimme Them Goodies and the Wrong Song
      Who Says You Always Have to Be Happy?
      Yenta Power
      Let Me Sing My Song
      Out-a-Town
      Jokes
      "Sneakers" Finale
      What We Go Through
      I've Been in Those Shoes
      Don't Tell Me
      Goin' to Broadway
      Be Like a Basketball and Bounce Right Back
    - The Boys from Syracuse (GLTF), Act I (Scene 2 through "Shortest"); ("Shortest Day"-Finale), undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611679)
    - La Cage Aux Folles, 1984, undated; 3 (Box 11)
      - La Cage Aux Folles, Act One (1 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611687)
      - La Cage Aux Folles, Act Two (2 of 3 audiocassettes), 1984 April 13; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611695)
      - La Cage, J. Herman plays and sings (3 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611703)
    - Candide, 1997; 1 (Box 11)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Consult Access Services for further information.
      This is a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
    - The Cigarette Song, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611711)
    - A Class Act, Act I and II, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611729)
      A list of contents is included.
      1. Light on My Feet
      2. Fountain in the Garden
      3. One More Beautiful Song
      4. Fridays at Four & Bobby's Song
      5. Charm Song
      6. Paris Through the Window
      7. Mona
      8. Making Up Ways
      9. Under Separate Cover
      10. Gauguin's Shoes
      11. Follow Your Star
      12. Better
      13. Scintillating Sophie
      14. Next Best Thing to Love
      15. Broadway Boogle Woogle
      16. One / Better (reprise) / I Choose You / Light on My Feet (reprise)
      17. Say Something Funny
      18. When the Dawn Breaks
      19. Self Portrait
    - Class Enemy, undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611737)
    - Collette, 1989, undated; 11
      - Collette Collage (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1989; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611745)
      - Collette, selections, Act 1 and 2 (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 11, Item barcode 39002104611752)
      - Collette Collage, Staged Reading, Act 1, P10, 1989 December 7; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612032)
      - Collette Collage, Staged Reading, Act 2, P11, 1989 December 7; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612040)
      - Collette Collage, Staged Reading, Act 1, P12, 1989 December 11; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612016)
      - Collette Collage, Staged Reading, Act 2, P13, 1989 December 11; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612024)
      - Collette, Act I, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612057)
      - Collette, Staged Reading, Act II, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612065)
      - Collette, read [through], Seattle, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612073)
      - Collette, Orch. 1, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612081)
      - Collette Collage, demo, Act I and II, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612099)
    - Company, 1970, undated; 6 (Box 12)
      - Company, run through, 1970 March 16; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612107)
      - Company, run through, 1970 March 16; 1; Audiocassette tape is completely unwound and missing entire plastic casing. (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612115)
      - Company, Act One, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612123)
      - Company, Act Two, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612131)
      - Company, (Live), Act I, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612149)
      - Company, (Live), Act II, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612156)
    - The Cradle Will Rock, 1960, undated; 2 (Box 12)
      - The Cradle Will Rock, undated; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612164)
      - The Cradle Will Rock, NYC Opera, 1960 February 11-14; 1 (Box 12, Item barcode 39002104612172)
    - Daarlin' Juno, 1976-1992; 5 (Box 13)
      - Daarlin' Juno, Act I, Long Wharf Theatre, 1976 June 11; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612198)
      - Daarlin' Juno, Act II, Long Wharf Theatre, 1976 June 11; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612206)
      - Daarlin' Juno, Tape #1, 1970 May 14-June 11; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612214)
      - Daarlin' Juno, Tape #2, 1976 May 14-June 11; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612222)
      - Juno, Musical Theater Lab, Tape One, 1992 August 27; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612230)
    - Dance A Little Closer, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612180)
    - Dance a Little Closer, Act II, undated; 1 (Box 20, Item barcode 39002104616785)
      Written in the liner notes: So long 174 St.
    - Dancing on the Air, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612321)
    - A Doll's Life, undated; 2 (Box 13)
      - A Doll's Life, Liza, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612339)
      - A Doll's Life, Betsy, II, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612347)
    - Duddy, 1984, undated; 4 (Box 13)
      - Duddy, Act One, Edmonton, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612248)
      - Duddy, Act Two, Edmonton, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612255)
      - Duddy, Act Two, Ottawa, 1984 June 2; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612263)
      - Duddy, Ottawa, closing night, 1984 June 2; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612271)
    - Durante, undated; 4 (Box 13)
      - Durante, Orchestra Reading, Tape One, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612289)
      - Durante, Orchestra Reading, Tape Two, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612297)
      - Durante, Acts I and II, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612305)
      - Durante, undated; 1 (Box 13, Item barcode 39002104612313)
        Side One / Side Two
        Overture
        People Would Laugh
        What a Day
        Put You Arms Around Me, Honey
        I'll Do the Strutaway
        Hello, Hello, Hello
        Jimmy, The Well-Dressed Man
        I Know Darn Well I Can Do Without Broadway
        Don't Lose Your Sense of Humor
        Jimmy at the Palace: You've Got to Start Off Each Day
        Jimmy at the Palace: I Love Ya, Love Ya, Love Ya
        Entra'acte
        Goodnight, Goodnight, Goodnight
        Just the Other Day
        Toot Toot Tootsie
        Did You Ever Have the Feeling You Wanted to Go?
        My One Room Home
        Partners
        Inka-Dinka-Doo
        We're the Men...
        Razzamatazz
        September Song
        Goodnight
        Exit Music
    - Dumb Cake [Duddy?], undated; 1; 00:40:19; The program is distorted at times. Previously recorded material can be heard in the right channel. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612479)
    - Evening Primrose, 2 (Box 14)
      - Evening Primrose; The Canterville Ghost, undated; 1; 01:34:20; The program is very distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is recorded at a very high level. High frequency noise can be heard on the tape. The right channel's audio was recorded at a lower level. Hum can be heard. Heavy interference and audio breakup can be heard in the last 49 minutes of the tape. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612487)
      - Evening Primrose, undated; 1; 00:45:06; High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is very distorted at times. High frequency noise can be heard. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612495)
    - The Exception and the Rule, A Pray by Blecht, Steven Sondheim and Leonard Bernstein; WNEW Interview with Sondheim on Yip Harburg, West Side Story, movie soundtrack, 1981 March 8; 1; 01:27:20; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. Right channel audio was recorded at a lower level for the last 25 minutes of the tape. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612503)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, undated; 2 (Box 14)
      - Fiddler on the Roof, Live, Act One, undated; 1; 01:34:00; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. The program begins and ends abruptly. Audio is unclear at times. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612511)
      - Fiddler on the Roof, Live, Act Two, undated; 1; 00:51:12; Audio is sometimes unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612529)
    - Finian's Rainbow, 1999 May 3; 2 (Box 14)
      - Reading 1, 1999 May 3; 1; This tape is completely blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612537)
      - Reading 2, 1999 May 3; 1; 00:53:18; The program is distorted at times. An echo in the audio can be heard at times on the tape. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower level. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612545)
    - Follies, undated; 11
      - Follies, creators and cast on The David Frost Show, [1971?]; 1; 01:09:39; The program begins and ends abruptly. The program is distorted at times. The audio is unclear at times. There is a high amount of buzz and hum on the tape. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612552)
      - Follies, Live NY - through "The Reads"; "Bolero" to "The Right Girl", undated; 1; 01:29:42; The program is distorted at times. A hum can be heard. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower level. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612560)
      - Follies, LA - Part One to "The Roads..."; to "The Right Girl", undated; 1; 01:30:13; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. Audio on the tape is sometimes unclear. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612578)
      - Follies, LA, Part Two - "One More Kiss" to finale, undated; 1; 00:45:44; The program is distorted at times. A high amount of hiss is on the tape. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower level. Warble can be heard on the tape. The program ends abruptly. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612586)
      - Follies, New York - Part Two - "One More Kiss" to bows; after piece, undated; 1; 01:01:12; The program is distorted at times. Levels of audio vary at times in the first 52 minutes of the program. Audio is sometimes unclear on the tape. A hum can be heard on the tape. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612594)
      - Follies, undated; 1; 01:31:15; A high amount of background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower level. Hum can be heard on the tape. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612602)
      - Follies, Pt. 2, undated; 1; 00:58:00; The program is distorted at times. An audio echo can be heard at times. A hum can be heard on the tape. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612610)
      - Follies, David Frost show, [1971?]; 1; 01:10:34; The program is distorted at times. A high amount of buzz and hum can be heard. The audio is unclear at times. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower level. High frequency background noise can be heard on the tape. The program ends abruptly. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612628)
      - Follies, Live-songs only, undated; 1; 01:37:01; The program is distorted at times. The program ends abruptly. (Box 14, Item barcode 39002104612636)
      - Follies, Live I, through "The roads"; through "The Right Girl", undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613550)
      - Follies, Live II, through "Losing My Mind", undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613568)
    - For Sherman By Sherman From Sherman, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613576)
      Not Enough
      I Love You, Dear
      It Comes to Me
      What Did She Look Like?
      You Never Had It So Good
      Franklin Shepard, Inc.
      Old Friends
      Good Thing Going
    - Four Jews in A Room Bitching, 2 (Box 15)
      - Lonny Price, 1980 April 29; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613584)
      - William Finn, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613592)
        There is a list of contents included with this audiocassette.
        4 Jews in a Room Bitching
        Love is Blind
        The Thrill of First Love
        Miss Goldberg's Philosophy of Love
        First Moses Monologue
        The Dinosaur Song
        Marvin at the Psychiatrist (Sorta Kinda, Miss Goldberg Over My Shoulder, Sorta Kinda)
        I Love You, Dear (A Marriage Proposal)
        The Disappearance of Miss Goldberg's Chest
        These are the Games I Play
        March of the Falsettos
        Hold Me Tight
        Trina is Lying in Bed
        Second Moses Monologue
        Makine a Home
        The 10 Commandments as Told by God to Maruin
        Maruin Hits Trina
        I Never Wanted to Love You
        I Love You, Dear (reprise)
        Love is Blind (finale)
    - Foxy, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613600)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (Box 15)
      - Live, Act II, 1973 April 9; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613618)
      - Phil Silvers, Act One, 1973 April 9; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613626)
      - Live, Pt. I, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613634)
      - Pt. II, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613642)
      - Pt. III, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613659)
    - Gantry demo, undated; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613667)
      The Promise of What I Could Be
      These Four Walls
      Someone I've Already Found
      She Was a Woman
      Foresight
      He's Never Too Busy
      Show Him the Way
      We Can All Give Love
    - The Girl Most Likely To..., Vocal Selections, Musical Theatre Works reading, 2000 August 22; 1 (Box 15, Item barcode 39002104613675)
      "Most Likely"
      "End of the Line"
      "Rules of the Pad"
      "The Man of Your Dreams"
      "Groovy People"
      "Verrone Comma Ralph"
      "My Sister"
      "Pigskin of the Past"
      "Pull an All Nighter"
      "Where is the Woman?"
      "It's Just a Joke"